>> Brian Holt: 好，最后，让我们去写我们的节点服务器。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, finally,
let's go write our node server.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，由于这是在 babble 中，我们可以使用导入语法。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So because this is in
babble, we can use import syntax.
所以我们要用快说的方式说进口
So we're gonna say import
express from express.
布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 你会说的另一件事是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
the other thing you're gonna call this is,
>> Brian Holt: 我在哪里放这个?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Where do I put this?
并在此文件夹中创建一个新目录。
And make a new directory
here inside of this folder.
不在源和被叫服务器内部
Not inside the source and called server,
因为你一般都想把你的前端和后端密码分开
because you generally want to keep your
front end and back end code separate,
然后我就把这个指数联系上了
and then I'm just going to
call this index touch as.
>> Brian Holt: 因此从 Express 中输入表示，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
import express from express,
反应的反应
import react from react,
从反应 - don/server 导入 renderToString ，
import renderToString
from react-don/server,
从每个路由器导入服务器位置。
import Server location
from at each router.
导入作为文件系统的 fs ，
Import fs which is a file system,
从 fs 到节点模块，以及
from fs to node module and
从 /src/App 导入应用程序。
import app from /src/App.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，首先你想确定这是什么港口
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, first thing is you
wanna identify what port this is gonna
运行，所以我们会说 const PORT = process.env.PORT。
run on, so we're gonna say
const PORT = process.env.PORT.
因此，您可以将端口设置为环境变量，并且
So you can either have the port set
an an environmental variable, and
如果他们没有设置任何东西，就将它设置为 3000。
if they don't set anything,
just set it to 3000.
只有 1000 以上的任意数字才会起作用。
Just any random number
above 1000 will work.
好吧我们要说 const html = fs.readFileSync。
Okay, we're going to say
const html = fs.readFileSync.
Disting/index.html.tostring， so
Dist/index.html.tostring, so
这就去读输出 html 的权利
this is going to go read
the output html right,
这样我们就能把它用在我们的服务器上
so that we could use that in our server
侧面渲染 >> Brian Holt: 然后
side rendering
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Then
你会把它分成两部分对吧
you're gonna split it into two parts,
right?
因此， const parts = split。
So const parts = split.
好，我们先看看这个。
Well, let's go take a look at this first.
如果我进入我的 index.html，我希望我的标记在哪里呢 ?
If I go into my index.html,
where do I want my markup to actually go?
我们希望它能到这里来对吧
We want it to go here in route, right?
所以我要做的有点棘手因为我刚装了
So what I'm gonna do is kind of be
a little tricky, because I just loaded
把这件事都做了我就会分得不怎么样
this whole thing as a string and
I'm going to split on not rendered, right.
所以它的第一部分就是所有这些，对。
So the first part of it is
going to be all of this, right.
第二部分就是这些，然后我把我的标记放在这里，
And the second part of it will be all of
this, then I'll put my mark up here, and
然后我先把第一部分放在首位
then I'll put the first part first,
the rendered mark up, and
然后是第二部分。
then the second part.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
所以我要把它分开
So I'm gonna say html.split not rendered.
> > Brian Holt: 那么现在我要有两部分，第一部分和
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So, now I'm gonna have
an array of two parts, the first part and
第二部分。
the second part.
>> Brian Holt: 您可以使用诸如 EJS或 Handlebar 之类的内容来执行此操作，或者
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You could do this with
something like EJS, or Handlebars, or
你甚至可以用 " 雷法 " 自己来做
you could even do it with React
itself to render this together.
这其实很简单，我觉得这也不是不好的做法。
This is really simple, and I think this
is not a bad way of doing it either.
我要说 const app = express，
I'm going to say const app = express,
来启动新的快速服务器
to start a new express server,
我要把 app.use/ dist 作为 express.static dist。
I'm gonna say app.use/ dist
as express.static dist.
所以这将会对 dist 目录中的所有内容进行静态处理，对吗 ?
So, this is gonna statically serve
everything in the dist directory, right?
那么， HTML， CSS， JavaScript 图像，
So, the HTML, CSS, JavaScript images,
所有这些都来自 dist 目录
all that is gonna come
from the dist directory.
我得说 app.use 然后我就给你
Here I'm gonna say app.use and
then I'm gonna give it
一个中间件，可以在每次请求时运行，好吗 ?
a middleware to run every single
time that it gets requested, okay?
我要说 const reattMarkup = ServerLocation。
Here I'm gonna say const
reactMarkup = ServerLocation.
因此，这来自 Reach 路由器以执行服务器站点呈现。
So this is from Reach Router to
do the server site rendering.
url =rec.url。
url =rec.url.
所以如果有人请求提供详细信息 /
So, if someone requests details/200,
那就是从快递过来的 URL
that'll be the URL coming
in from express and
然后你就把应用放进去
then you'll put app inside of that and
然后你就会在这里说重发
then down here you're gonna say res.send.
我要在这里做三部分
I'm going to do three parts here.
>> Brian Holt: 您可以说 0 部分加上
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You could say parts 0 plus
对字符串进行反应标记。
render to string react markup.
+ parts[1]， right?
+ parts[1], right?
HTML 的第一部分，呈示标记， HTML 的第二部分。
First part of the HTML, rendered markup,
second part of the HTML.
然后你会说 res.end()， > > Brian Holt: 好的，
And then here, you're gonna say res.end();
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
你就会说 console.log
then you'll say console.log.
在 PORT 和
Listening on PORT and
表示 app.listen(PORT)。
say app.listen(PORT).
>> Brian Holt: 因此，如果您不太了解节点的部分，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So if you don't know
too much about the nodes part of that,
那就好
that's totally fine.
这里有很多关于这个的课程
There's plenty of courses
on here about that but
是否有任何关于 " 反应 " 部分的问题 ?
are there any questions about
the React portions of this?
这就是如何让它起作用的核心部分。
This is kind of the core part of
how to get this to work with react.
你把它放在服务器上
You render it on the server, and
你会把它作为完整的标记发送给客户
you're gonna send it down to
the client as complete markup.
所以，让我们给你一个机会，但你需要两个包装才能做到这一点。
So let's give a shot, but
you're gonna need two packages to do this.
你需要快递你会说 npm 的安装
You're gonna need express,
you're gonna say npm install.
然后，您还需要 @babel/node。
Express and
then you're also gonna need @babel/node.
所以这个是一个通用的 js 框架，
So this one is a common js framework and
这一系统将允许您通过 Babel 运行所有节点代码。
this one is going to allow you to run all
your node code through Babel as well.
因此 >> Brian Holt: 可以
So
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Can
从那个不太重要的 .js 中删除
delete that as well from that .js,
that's not super important.
还有一件事要解决 package.json
One more thing to fix as
well in package.json,
请记住，我们从客户机应用程序切换到现在是浏览器条目。
remember we switch from client app
to now being the browser entry.
所以我们也要做建筑，
So we have to also do build,
不构建，但在 index.html 中
not build but in index.html
就是这么说的
that's what it is.
在这里，我们要指出的是 ClientApp。
Here instead of being client app,
we're going to point this out ClientApp.
与其作为应用，我们将把它指向 ClientApp。
Instead of it being app,
we're going to point it at ClientApp.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，如果我们开始
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now if we start and
再次停止服务器，
stop the server again,
运行开始，现在应该开始工作了。
pm run start, now this should work.
>> Brian Holt: 好，现在所有的 JavaScript 都在工作。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay so
now all the JavaScript is working as well.
> > Brian Holt: 但我想在这里提出的观点，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
the point that I wanted to bring up here,
如果我在此处再次查看此页面，请在我的视图源中查看。
if I look at this page again
here in My view source.
还像所有正确的代码一样加载吗 ?
It's still loading like all
the correct code here as well right?
所以它还在做服务端的渲染。
And so
it's still doing service side rendering.
每个路由都在执行相应的操作，因为每个路由器都在
It's doing the appropriate one per route
because each router is taking in that
URL 并呈现正确的页面吗?
url and rendering the correct page Right?
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我们可以定义浏览器中的所有路由
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So we get to define all
of our routes inside of the browser
客户机端渲染器，但是仍然能够使用所有相同的路由，
client-side renderer, but notice still
able to use all the same routes,
这很酷
which is cool.